<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Johnny's</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/categories/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Johnny's</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 20:03:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lijohnny.com/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Switch from Hexo to Hugo</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/p/switch-from-hexo-to-hugo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 20:03:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lijohnny.com/p/switch-from-hexo-to-hugo/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a year since last time I update my blog. Recently, I want to get back to writing blog again. However, I encounter some issues.
Hexo, the static web generator I used, was not compatible with current node.js version in my system.
Somehow node.js was extremely slow in WSL2.
I prefer working with the language that I&amp;rsquo;m more familiar with.
Therefore, I start looking for other solutions.</description></item><item><title>Automate Image Processing for My Blog</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/p/automate-image-processing-for-my-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 22:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lijohnny.com/p/automate-image-processing-for-my-blog/</guid><description>&lt;p>As you can see, my blog contains cover images. Every time I write an article I need to upload a cover image to the image server. However, the process is complicated and trivial. I need to crop the image to a certain proportion and resize and compress the image to reduce the loading time. Moreover, to put the photographer&amp;rsquo;s name on the image, I need to use other software. Therefore, I create two python scripts to automate the process.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Solve the Problem in a April Fool's Joke</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/p/solve-the-problem-in-a-april-fools-joke/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 14:35:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lijohnny.com/p/solve-the-problem-in-a-april-fools-joke/</guid><description>On April 1st, one of the post on v2ex (An online community of developers and designers in China1) become viral. The post title is &amp;ldquo;Seeking Dates&amp;rdquo; and it is posted on April 1st, so most reactions of this post are pointing out that this is the &amp;ldquo;new trap&amp;rdquo; of the recruiters.
Here is the translation:
I am born and raised in Hangzhou. I am a science student at Zhejiang University &amp;hellip; I hope to find a man can pass the following test.</description></item></channel></rss>