<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Analysis on Johnny's Blog</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/tags/data-analysis/</link><description>Recent content in Data Analysis on Johnny's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 19:56:44 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lijohnny.com/tags/data-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pyforest - Automate Package Import Process for Your Data Science Project</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/p/pyforest-automate-package-import-process-for-your-data-science-project/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 19:56:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://lijohnny.com/p/pyforest-automate-package-import-process-for-your-data-science-project/</guid><description>Usually, the first step we all do for any Python project is importing required packages. So, the beginning of the file usually looks like this:
import xxxx as xxx from xxxx import xxxx Importing packages is one of my least favorite parts when I&amp;rsquo;m working on a Data Scientist project. Packages like pandas, numpy, lighteda, matplotlib.pyplot, and seaborn are commonly used for my projects. I need to repeat this step in every single Jupyter Notebook.</description></item><item><title>Identify Customer Segments</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/p/identify-customer-segments/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 21:42:22 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://lijohnny.com/p/identify-customer-segments/</guid><description>This is one of the Udacity Data Scientist Nanodegree Project. This project aims to identify segments of the population from the core customer base for a mail-order sales company in Germany. Therefore, these segments can then be used to direct marketing campaigns towards audiences with the highest expected rate of returns.
The techniques I used in this project include:
Data cleaning Encoding and processing mixed-type feature Feature Scaling and Dimensionality Reduction Clustering Performance improvement with OpenBLAS You can find the full analysis in my GitHub repo.</description></item></channel></rss>