<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Automation on Johnny's Blog</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/tags/automation/</link><description>Recent content in Automation on Johnny's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 19:56:44 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lijohnny.com/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pyforest - Automate Package Import Process for Your Data Science Project</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/p/pyforest-automate-package-import-process-for-your-data-science-project/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 19:56:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://lijohnny.com/p/pyforest-automate-package-import-process-for-your-data-science-project/</guid><description>Usually, the first step we all do for any Python project is importing required packages. So, the beginning of the file usually looks like this:
import xxxx as xxx from xxxx import xxxx Importing packages is one of my least favorite parts when I&amp;rsquo;m working on a Data Scientist project. Packages like pandas, numpy, lighteda, matplotlib.pyplot, and seaborn are commonly used for my projects. I need to repeat this step in every single Jupyter Notebook.</description></item><item><title>Automate Image Processing for My Blog</title><link>https://lijohnny.com/p/automate-image-processing-for-my-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 22:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lijohnny.com/p/automate-image-processing-for-my-blog/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>:warning:The old cript is &lt;code>DEPRECATED&lt;/code>. I switch to FastAPI, and updated the code &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/iamjohnnyli/blog-image-processing-automation" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a>. The old code is now in &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/iamjohnnyli/blog-image-processing-automation/tree/V1.0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>v1.0 Branch&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>As you can see, my blog contains cover images. Every time I write an article I need to upload a cover image to the image server. However, the process is complicated and trivial. I need to crop the image to a certain proportion and resize and compress the image to reduce the loading time. Moreover, to put the photographer&amp;rsquo;s name on the image, I need to use other software. Therefore, I create two python scripts to automate the process.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>